Hubungi

www.linkedin.com/in/triardysw (LinkedIn)

Keahlian Teratas

Data Analysis
Statistics
Data Visualization

Certifications

DeepLearning.AI TensorFlow
Developer Specialization
Tableau Fundamentals
Google IT Automation with Python
Data Scientist with R Track
Mathematics for Machine Learning
Specialization

Triardy S.

Data Analyst Associate at Tokopedia Sidoarjo

Ringkasan

I am graduated in statistics with honors from a reputable university. I was experienced in statistics and data modeling using statistical tools like R and python. Already have some certificate from several courses and still upgrading my technical skill in data science and analytics through online classes.

Pengalaman

PT Tokopedia
Data Analyst
Oktober 2021 - Present (9 bulan)
Jakarta Selatan, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

My role as Data Analyst focused on Customer Excellence. I've done some analysis related to Chatbot's performance and already built some dashboards to monitor metrics in the operations team's

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka Machine Learning Path Student Februari 2021 - Juli 2021 (6 bulan)

Doing Courses in both self-learning and live-online class. Learn material about how to become a good Machine Learning Engineer with a certificate from Tensorflow. Our final project is about doing forecasting revenue based on historical dataset of a UKM using LSTM deep learning model.

Universitas Brawijaya Assistant of Computational Statistics Course September 2020 - Desember 2020 (4 bulan) Malang, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Teach students in the course about how to deal with data using R, introducing data type in R, read kind of data format, cleaning, wrangling, and modeling data.

Badan Pusat Statistik Student Internship Juli 2020 - Agustus 2020 (2 bulan)

Malang, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Jobdesk: Make a yearbook about descriptive statistics in Kota Malang Student Final Report: Forecasting open unemployment rate in Jawa Timur using Outlier Model in R

Universitas Brawijaya Assistant of Advanced Regression Analysis Course Februari 2020 - Mei 2020 (4 bulan) Malang, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Mentoring students in this course about how to modeling ridge regression, principal component regression, and non-linear regression model, and how to implement it using statistical software (Minitab, SPSS, R)

Pendidikan

Universitas Brawijaya
Bachelor's degree, Statistics · (Agustus 2017 - Juli 2021)

SMA Negeri 1 Porong
Ilmu Alam (Natural Sciences) · (2014 - 2017)